Finding Aid for the Louis B. Schnauber (Film Music Society) Collection PASC-M.0157
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Venetian Love Dance (Box 10, Folder 921)
- Venetian Waters (Box 7, Folder 642)
- Venus on Earth (Box 3, Folder 299)
- The Victorious Phalanx, 1911 (Box 9, Folder 805)
- Victor Herbert (Box 9, Folder 802)
- Vienna Beauties (Box 8, Folder 777)
- Vienna Bloods (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Viennese (Box 3, Folder 281)
- The Viking March, 1911; 12 p. (Box 5, Folder 430)
- The Village Blacksmith (Box 10, Folder 920)
- Villanelle (Box 10, Folder 919)
- Villanelle (Box 11, Folder 972)
- Village Green (Box 1, Folder 102)
- Violin Sonata No. 2. Allegretto (Box 7, Folder 591)
- Virginia Diggins (Box 7, Folder 606)
- Vision (Box 10, Folder 922)
- Vision d'Amour (Box 10, Folder 925)
- Visions (Box 1, Folder 100)
- Vive L'Amerique (Box 3, Folder 278)
- The Vixen (Box 8, Folder 759)
- Vorspiel (Box 11, Folder 962)
- Wait Till You Get Them in the Air, Boys (Box 7, Folder 618)
- Waiting For You (Box 4, Folder 377)
- Wake Up, America! (Box 6, Folder 500)
- A Waltz Dream (Box 4, Folder 307)
- The Walkover (Box 4, Folder 311)
- A Warmin' Up in Dixie (Box 10, Folder 906)
- Was I Just Another Love Affair To You (Box 4, Folder 346)
  Also composed by Al Lewis and Al Sherman.
- Was It A Dream?, 1928; 12 p. (Box 2, Folder 139)
  Also composed by Larry Spier and Addy Britt.
- unspecified (Box 10, Folder 939)
- Water Lillies (Box 10, Folder 926)
- Water Sprites (Box 10, Folder 939)
- Waves of the Danube Waltzes (Box 33, Folder 11)
- Way Out Yonder In the Golden West (Box 6, Folder 582)
- Wayside Flowers (Box 10, Folder 933)
- We Have Much To Be Thankful For (Box 6, Folder 578)
- The Wedding of Heinie and Katharina (Box 10, Folder 917)
- Wedding March (Box 10, Folder 938)
- Wedding Ring, 1911 (Box 8, Folder 674)
- Wedding Day at Troldhaugen (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Weird Oriental Theme (Box 6, Folder 551)
- Were You Sincere? (Box 8, Folder 689)
- Western American Drama. Prelude (Box 10, Folder 904)
- When It's Moonlight on the Alamo (Box 9, Folder 817)
- When Shadows Fall, 1927 (Box 8, Folder 691)
- Where My Caravan Has Rested (Box 8, Folder 711)
- When I Take My Sugar To Tea (Box 3, Folder 255)
  Also composed by Irving Kahal and Pierre Norman
- When Love Comes Stealing (Box 3, Folder 298)
  Also composed by Lew Pollack and Walter Hirsch
- When Shall We Meet Again (Box 7, Folder 620)
- When the Cherry Blossoms Fall (Box 4, Folder 338)
- When the Gold is Tinged With Gray (Box 4, Folder 333)
- When the Harvest Moon Is Shining (Box 4, Folder 341)
- When the Roses Bloom Again in Normandy (Box 3, Folder 267)
- When the Roses Bloom Again in Normandy, 1931 (Box 8, Folder 687)
- When the Shadows Fall (Box 3, Folder 295)
- Where the Blue of the Night Meets the Gold of the Day (Box 6, Folder 536)
  Also composed by Bing Crosby and Fred E. Ahlert.
- Where the Ganges Flows (Box 1, Folder 86)
- Whispering Hearts (Box 7, Folder 612)
- Whispering Hope (Alice Hawthorne), 1925 (Box 11, Folder 941)
- Whispering Willows (Box 10, Folder 927)
- Who Am I? (Box 6, Folder 540)
- Who's Who in Navy Blue (Box 4, Folder 337)
- The Whole World is Waiting, 1927 (Box 8, Folder 692)
  Also composed by Deane Moore.
- Why? (Box 10, Folder 927)
- Why Don't You Answer Me? (Box 8, Folder 700)
- Why Shouldn't I (Box 4, Folder 353)
- Wild Rosebud (Box 11, Folder 942)
- William Tell Me (Box 1, Folder 9)
- The Winning Fight, 1911 (Box 8, Folder 681)
- Wings of Joy (Box 10, Folder 940)
- Wine, Women and Song (Box 34, Folder 14)
- Wisteria (Box 7, Folder 608)
- Witches' Dance (Box 10, Folder 935)
- With Pleasure-Galop, 1888 (Box 8, Folder 773)
- Withered Flowers No. 41 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- The Woodland Inn (Box 10, Folder 936)
- Woodland Whispers (Box 10, Folder 934)
- World's Peace, 1919 (Box 8, Folder 680)
- The World is Waiting for the Sunrise (Box 3, Folder 241)
- The World's Progress (Box 7, Folder 665)
- Wrap Your Troubles In Dreams (Box 3, Folder 253)
  Also composed by Billy Moll and Harry Barris
- Wyoming (Box 3, Folder 294)
- Ya Got Love! (Box 4, Folder 348)
  Also composed by Ed Nelson and Al Hoffman.
- Yearning (Box 10, Folder 928)
- Yellow Jasmine. The Angel Guardian, 1916; 14 parts (Box 13)
- Yelva (Box 32, Folder 14)
- Yes Sir, That's My Baby (Box 7, Folder 617)
  Also composed by Walter Donaldson.
- Yes! We Have No Bananas (Box 8, Folder 750)
  Also composed by Irving Cohn.
- Yester-Love (Box 10, Folder 937)
- Yo San (Box 6, Folder 555)
- "Young Werner's Parting Song". "Then You'll Remember Me". The Lost Chord, 1907; 13 parts (Box 13)
- You Can Have It, I Don't Want It (Box 9, Folder 841)
  Also composed by Williams and Piron.
- You Only Want Me When Nobody Else Is Around (Box 6, Folder 531)
  Also composed by Johnny Burke.
- You Tell Her = I Stutter (Box 8, Folder 740)
- You'll Have to Put Him to Sleep With the Marseillaise and Wake Him Up With a Oo-La-La, 1918; 9 p. (Box 5, Folder 414)
- Your Absence is Breaking My Heart (Box 6, Folder 576)
- Your Eyes Have Told Me So (Box 8, Folder 702)
  Also composed by Van Alstyne and Blaufuss.
- You're the Dawn of a Perfect Day (Box 6, Folder 579)
- You're My Everything (Box 6, Folder 535)
- You're the Only Girl that Made Me Cry (Box 6, Folder 516)
- Youth and Beauty (Box 7, Folder 650)
- Ypsilanti (Box 6, Folder 575)
  Also written by Van Alstyne.
- Zinnia (Box 4, Folder 375)